<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Raptoreum Docs Blog</title>
        <link>https://humbledeer.github.io/raptoreum-docs/blog</link>
        <description>Raptoreum Docs Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 05:42:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Testing all author tags]]></title>
            <link>https://humbledeer.github.io/raptoreum-docs/blog/test-all-authors</link>
            <guid>test-all-authors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 05:42:40 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Testing all the authors]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="testing-all-the-authors">Testing all the authors<a class="hash-link" href="#testing-all-the-authors" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>123</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>rtm</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feathered For Growth]]></title>
            <link>https://humbledeer.github.io/raptoreum-docs/blog/feathered-for-growth</link>
            <guid>feathered-for-growth</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 05:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Feathered For Growth Banner]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" alt="Feathered For Growth Banner" src="/raptoreum-docs/assets/images/feathered-for-growth-7eed2de45f948231f72e480fe88213db.png" width="1280" height="463" class="img_ev3q"></p><p>We have huge aspirations to take the next important steps needed for the growth of Raptoreum into the new cycles and beyond, and one of those steps is incorporation.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="feathered-corp">Feathered corp<a class="hash-link" href="#feathered-corp" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>Feathered Corp was created by the RTM Core Team members Paul Mills (aka Binarai) and David Morris (BigPiggy01), and was needed in order to move forward with progressing major Raptoreum partnerships.</p><p>Some of the largest exchanges in the world required the Raptoreum project to have a permanent base. After months of research on location, Seychelles was chosen for being free from stifling regulations that hinder and hamper innovation without any tradition of regulatory overreach. The tax status of an IBC registered in Seychelles also provides an unfettered environment in which we can grow the project as well and handle any potential Intellectual Property issues that may or may not arise.</p><p>Now that this is in place, we are excited to be able to do things and make connections like we never have before. We called it <em>‘Feathered’</em> as this allows us to stretch our wings into multiple areas of growth, allowing interconnections within the Raptoreum project under one umbrella. In a time of uncertainty, larger players in the field are looking for trust in a team and accountability to support their own projects, due to the lessons learnt from a historically bad previous financial cycle and the detrimental executive choices of some select coins.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="the-future-of-raptoreum">The future of Raptoreum<a class="hash-link" href="#the-future-of-raptoreum" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>With our upcoming code releases and projects already building on our blockchain, it is important that nothing holds us back from realizing our goals in providing a full suite of tools for the worlds community of developers. Clearing the road legally for a bump in market cap standings is one of those goals, with all the juicy bits as fruits of our labour.</p><p>Raptoreum is deep in our hearts and we have always done everything by the book. We never have <strong>and never will</strong> cut a single corner to achieve short term success. We believe in the long term sustainability, where the true value of work conducted by the team and the community shines in a real, organic way. Even in the darkest days of a bear market, our communities have shown to be some of the busiest in the world; We think that is a testament of whats to come!</p><p>It is a pleasure to bring this great news to you all. LONG LIVE RAPTOREUM!</p><p><em>HUGE thanks to Zlata Amaranth for the awesome branding and artwork.</em></p><p>Thank you <!-- -->-<!-- --> The Raptoreum Team</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>featheredcorp</category>
            <category>feathered</category>
            <category>company</category>
            <category>registration</category>
            <category>growth</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Raptoreum Futures are here!]]></title>
            <link>https://humbledeer.github.io/raptoreum-docs/blog/futures-mainnet-release</link>
            <guid>futures-mainnet-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 04:27:35 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Raptoreum Futures Mainnet Banner]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" alt="Raptoreum Futures Mainnet Banner" src="/raptoreum-docs/assets/images/futures-mainnet-release-3a4312cdaeb440171cc1c7aa6507a32e.png" width="1280" height="463" class="img_ev3q"></p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="we-did-it-marty">We did it, Marty!<a class="hash-link" href="#we-did-it-marty" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>After some <strong>HUGE</strong> development from the team, Raptoreum Futures Mainnet code had been released with RaptoreumCore version 1.3.17.0. Raptoreum Futures intend to be the first major foundation which will allow our eventual Smart Contracts, Assets and Blockchain to be one of the most advanced in the world.</p><p><strong>Download it here:</strong> <a href="https://github.com/Raptor3um/raptoreum/releases/tag/1.13.17.0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Release 1.13.17.0</a> (GitHub)</p><div class="theme-admonition theme-admonition-important alert alert--info admonition_LlT9"><div class="admonitionHeading_tbUL"><span class="admonitionIcon_kALy"><svg viewBox="0 0 14 16"><path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M7 2.3c3.14 0 5.7 2.56 5.7 5.7s-2.56 5.7-5.7 5.7A5.71 5.71 0 0 1 1.3 8c0-3.14 2.56-5.7 5.7-5.7zM7 1C3.14 1 0 4.14 0 8s3.14 7 7 7 7-3.14 7-7-3.14-7-7-7zm1 3H6v5h2V4zm0 6H6v2h2v-2z"></path></svg></span>Important</div><div class="admonitionContent_S0QG"><p><strong>Update your wallet before block 420420!</strong></p></div></div><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="changes-fixes-and-features">Changes, Fixes, and Features<a class="hash-link" href="#changes-fixes-and-features" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>Updates include numerous RPC changes as well as backports form BTC 17 and 18 as well as updates and upgrades to most of the Dash features!
From block 420420, RTM “futures” will bring changes to changes to the following <strong>RPC functions</strong>:</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="createrawtransaction"><code>createrawtransaction</code><a class="hash-link" href="#createrawtransaction" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>with additional fields being available for the addition of block based or time based lock times.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="sendtoaddress"><code>sendtoaddress</code><a class="hash-link" href="#sendtoaddress" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>with additional fields being available for the addition of block based or time based lock times.</p><p>Additionally, the following changes have been made to the RaptoreumCore code</p><ul><li>The Fee Setting spork has been added, to prevent any future "gas crisis" situations.</li><li>RaptoreumCore bootstrapping using POW cache has been implemented, reducing wallet sync times significantly. POW cache packages can be found on the <a href="https://bootstrap.raptoreum.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Raptoreum Bootstrap Packages</a> archive.</li><li>Various visual bug fixes on the QT Wallet</li><li>Optimizations for wallets with large amounts of transactions</li><li>Significantly more efficient threaded workload handling</li></ul><p>Apart from the above mentioned RTM changes, this update brings a plethora of changes over from the original Dash code. The full details on the Dash release can be found <a href="https://github.com/dashpay/dash/blob/v0.17.0.2/doc/release-notes.md" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here (Dash Core 0.17.0.2)</a>.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="important-notes">Important Notes<a class="hash-link" href="#important-notes" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>Dual checksums for reach release are packaged with the zip-archives for each operating system respectively. Remember to check both checksums. There have been reports of prior instances of malware in some wallet's files modified to meet single file checksum verifications.</p><div class="theme-admonition theme-admonition-danger alert alert--danger admonition_LlT9"><div class="admonitionHeading_tbUL"><span class="admonitionIcon_kALy"><svg viewBox="0 0 12 16"><path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M5.05.31c.81 2.17.41 3.38-.52 4.31C3.55 5.67 1.98 6.45.9 7.98c-1.45 2.05-1.7 6.53 3.53 7.7-2.2-1.16-2.67-4.52-.3-6.61-.61 2.03.53 3.33 1.94 2.86 1.39-.47 2.3.53 2.27 1.67-.02.78-.31 1.44-1.13 1.81 3.42-.59 4.78-3.42 4.78-5.56 0-2.84-2.53-3.22-1.25-5.61-1.52.13-2.03 1.13-1.89 2.75.09 1.08-1.02 1.8-1.86 1.33-.67-.41-.66-1.19-.06-1.78C8.18 5.31 8.68 2.45 5.05.32L5.03.3l.02.01z"></path></svg></span>Avoid negative lock times</div><div class="admonitionContent_S0QG"><p>Avoid setting both <em>lock times</em> as negative to prevent indefinitely locking your assets. More info available on the <a href="/raptoreum-docs/docs/raptoreum/futures.md">futures docs</a> soon.</p></div></div><p>Thank you <!-- -->-<!-- --> The Raptoreum Team</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>futures</category>
            <category>feathered</category>
            <category>mainnet</category>
            <category>release</category>
            <category>code</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use Cases in Feathered Futures]]></title>
            <link>https://humbledeer.github.io/raptoreum-docs/blog/use-cases-futures</link>
            <guid>use-cases-futures</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 04:04:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Futures Use Cases Banner]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" alt="Futures Use Cases Banner" src="/raptoreum-docs/assets/images/use-cases-in-feathered-futures-77b46c51d073e7262c10d8953fb939e2.png" width="1280" height="463" class="img_ev3q"></p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="what-is-a-futures-transaction">What is a Futures Transaction?<a class="hash-link" href="#what-is-a-futures-transaction" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><p>A futures transaction is the ability to send Raptoreum coins or a potential asset created on the Raptoreum blockchain to another wallet but have the balance unlock based on a ‘future’ timestamp or block height.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="potential-use-cases-in-feathered-futures">Potential Use cases In Feathered Futures<a class="hash-link" href="#potential-use-cases-in-feathered-futures" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="an-apartment-coming-up-for-rent-3-months-from-today">An Apartment coming up for rent 3 months from today<a class="hash-link" href="#an-apartment-coming-up-for-rent-3-months-from-today" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>and you want to rent it at current price assuring there will be no price increase. The building owner agrees to lock it in but needs assurance that you will indeed pay for it in 3 months. Futures asset transaction is sent to landlords RTM Asset address for full amount set to unlock at an exact timestamp in 3 months time.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="a-father-wishes-to-gift">A Father wishes to gift<a class="hash-link" href="#a-father-wishes-to-gift" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>some RTM to his son to help with living costs while at university, but would rather his son receive a smaller amount every month so he doesn’t spend it all at once. Futures are sent to his sons RTM address to unlock each month thereafter.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="a-cloud-mining-contract">A Cloud Mining Contract<a class="hash-link" href="#a-cloud-mining-contract" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>is funded and terminated based on a futures transaction of a set RTM blockchain height. After an initial collateralized contract starts, it is ‘topped’ up with an additional futures transaction at the the initial contract expiry time in order to keep the service running without a hitch.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="a-cloud-server">A Cloud Server<a class="hash-link" href="#a-cloud-server" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>is collateralized with RTM and then set to auto renew on the date of expiry with a futures transaction.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="a-selection-of-laser-scanned-nft-assets">A Selection of Laser Scanned NFT Assets<a class="hash-link" href="#a-selection-of-laser-scanned-nft-assets" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>created by a famous game studio upon the Raptoreum chain are – set to release to subscribers in stages based on time locked futures transactions distributing much anticipated content automatically, securely and on time.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="a-python-based-smart-contract">A Python based Smart Contract<a class="hash-link" href="#a-python-based-smart-contract" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>is deployed on an RTM SmartNode by a third party project built on the Raptoreum chain and is connected to a users app. When the users’ account reaches a birthday timestamp it executes premade futures transactions which are periodically taken from a fraction of the app subscription fee – rewarding the user for continued use of the app while unlocking additional features and fee rates automatically.</p><h3 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="a-leading-pr-news-platform">A Leading PR News Platform<a class="hash-link" href="#a-leading-pr-news-platform" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h3><p>(which recently integrated operations into the RTM blockchain through smart contracts in common languages) notified its close advertising partners that it will release a news article that will prove to be very popular.</p><p>It deploys futures timeslots to its clients for pre approved advertisements on the page of the upcoming article whom bid to fill on its decentralized digital advertising real estate marketplace dapp. If they win the bid,  they connect their wallet and submit their advert along with the required collateral of the RTM Chain created PRNEWS token.</p><p>Sending through the app initiates a futures based smart contract which carries the data of its initiation, its duration, its content and its collateral amount allowing the whole process to happen automatically by directly connecting the action of creation with the reaction or result.</p><p>With futures already fully coded at Raptoreum protocol level, the scope of potential development and creativity is extremely broad when combined with the activation of upcoming smart contracts in common languages such as Java, Python and Scala.  Raptoreum is building the tools for the next generation.</p><p>Thank you <!-- -->-<!-- --> The Raptoreum Team</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>futures</category>
            <category>feathered</category>
            <category>usecase</category>
            <category>features</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>